35 year old Punit knows his
responsibilities will increase with age
he chooses a life cover of one crore
rupees but increases by five percent
every year for the next 20 years to
cover the most crucial years at the age
of 55 his life cover would become two
crore rupees as his responsibilities
start decreasing his life cover becomes
one crore rupees between the ages of 56
to 60. as his responsibilities are
further reduced his life cover becomes
50 lakh rupees between the age of 61 to
75 years on Survival at age 75 his
policy lapses and he receives a total
payout of 11 lakhs 43 000 rupees as
return of Premium on his demise at age
54 his family will get one crore 95 lakh
rupees take an informed decision like
puneet choose ice cica Pro I protect
return of Premium with life stage cover
now